They can taste your fear.
Anaconda 3: Offspring is a horror, adventure, thriller
film directed by Don E. FauntLeRoy.
A mercenary-for-hire accepts a mission from a billionaire to capture a
dangerous snake that could possibly help cure a terminal illness.
Hammet, played by David Hasselhoff.
Dr. Amanda Hayes, played by Crystal Allen.
Peter "J.D." Murdoch, played by John Rhys-Davies.
Pinkus, played by Ryan McCluskey.
Nik, played by Patrick Regis.
Captain Grozny, played by Anthony Green.
Anaconda 3: Offspring is a 2008 adventure horror
television film directed by Don E.
FauntLeRoy and stars David Hasselhoff, Crystal Allen, and John Rhys-Davies.
The film is a sequel to Anacondas: The Hunt for the Blood Orchid (2004)
and the third installment in the Anaconda film series.
The film premiered on Sci Fi on July 26, 2008.
It was followed by Anacondas: Trail of Blood (2009).
The film explores themes of human vs nature, snake,
expedition, mercenary, survival.
The tone is dark and intense.